LO MANTO FABRIZIO

HANDYMAN / DRIVER / SOFTWARE DEV



- Driving Licence B
- **₩** 07/11/1986
- +34610953469
- ✓ lomfabrizio@hotmail.com
- https://lomfabrizio.duckdns.org/
- **♀** 38660 Costa Adeje

SKILLS

Language

French, Italian, English

Computer

Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Dev IDE

Eclipse, Ansys SCADE Suite, Atmel studio, Visual Studio Code

Programing language

c/c++ Linux, Python, Shell Script, SCADE, HTML5, CSS

CERTIFICATIONS

2022: BEPS (European First Aid Certificate)

2018: Pragmagora: conflict management, team-building and teamworking.

INTERESTS

DIY, home automation, electronics, 3D printing, sports, dance

INFO

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Handyman

Hardworking and experienced Handyman able to perform a variety of maintenance duties with skill. Adept in handling basic repairs, cosmetic upkeep, and simple appliance installations. Bringing forth the ability to handle power tools and some maintenance related machinery. Friendly and committed to providing top-notch services.

Driver

Dedicated and dependable Car Driver. Stickler for punctuality and safety. Established history of completing driving through various kinds of territory at various lengths.

Software developer

Software developer specialized in embedded systems, enthusiast by electronics, home automation on Linux, Micro-controller (pic, esp, avr), sensors and wireless communications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

• FN Herstal (internal): Senior developer system departement (R&D)

Active software developer in R&D department, design, development and maintenance of armory management and its derivatives

2018 - 2022

Project: deFNder Medium/Light new generation

Akka Benelux (Consultant FN Hertstal), team leader/architect/project coordinator, system

Team leader, Architect and Project coordinator in R&D department, development and maintenance for a simulator

2015 - 2017

project : deFNder Simulator

• Open Engineering (Consultant FN Hertstal), junior developer, system departement (R&D)

Active junior software developer in R&D department, design, development and maintenance

2012 - 2015

deFNder Medium/Light old generation

EDUCATION

• Haute école de la province de Liège : INPRES Seraing

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science & Systems, industrial computer science major

2007 - 2011

- Study and practice of the OEE module of Simatic IT (SIMENS).

• Ecole polytechnique de Herstal

Electronic technician

2000 - 2007

- Transmission / Reception of the RC5 Protocol (Philips) based on PIC